4thegame.com 2008-12-04

# 

**_Definitions:_  
**Us/We:** FastWeb Media Ltd  
**You:** The user of 4thegame.com / member of 4thegame Members Area**

Fast Web Media Ltd is committed to your right to privacy and will only use your data as set out in our privacy policy below. Please read this information carefully. By using 4thegame.com you agree to us collecting and using your personal information in accordance with the details below. 

1\. What information will we collect about you?  
We will collect information about you when you register to join the 4thegame Members Area, when you enter competitions and when you contact us or through the use of cookies. This may include information about how you use the Site. Though the privacy policy below has been developed to take account of the rapid development of Internet technology it is subject to change. Any such changes will be notified on this page. 

2\. What are cookies? Does 4thegame.com use cookies?  
When you use the 4thegame.com site we may automatically issue your computer with a small piece of code (a 'cookie'). Cookies are files we transfer to your computer's hard disk. Cookies can store information about your preferences on products and services and other information which you access when you visit the Site. We can use cookies to show us how you are using our Site and to collect demographic or statistical information about user behaviour. They allow us to analyse the popularity of the Site and to better manage and improve the service we provide to you. We also use ad servers to serve the advertisements that you see on the pages of our web site. You may also be issued with a cookie as part of this process. For information on changing your cookie settings: click here

3\. How will we use the information we collect about you?  
In order to use the 4thegame.com site you are not required to register or provide any personal information about yourself. 

You may however choose to join the 4thegame Members Area when you must register with us when we will collect and record the data you give us when registering or when you use the Site. Registration may also be necessary to enable you to participate in a competition, give-away or survey. As part of the registration process we may ask you to provide some limited personal information about yourself such as your name, address and e-mail and other information which we will use to better develop our Site to your needs. 

We will use the personal information you provide:  

  * to supply and manage the services you have asked us to provide to you;

  * to improve and develop the service or products we offer by analysing your information;

  * and to learn more about you so that we can identify products and services which may be of interest to you which we will tell you about unless you have requested us not to do so.

4\. Will we share your information with anyone else?  
We will share your information with other companies, who will be able to use it for assessment and analysis (including market and product analysis). Unless you tell us that you do not wish to receive information from us or other companies, your information may be used by us or other companies to tell you (by letter, phone (including automated dialling), fax, digital television, e-mail or SMS) about products and services (including those of others) which may be of interest to you. 

We do at times need to pass on your information to people who provide services to us (although this is only done on the understanding that your information is kept confidential). Data may also be disclosed to anyone to whom we transfer our rights or duties under this agreement, if there is a legal duty to disclose or if the law allows it. 

5\. How long will Fast Web Media Ltd keep your personal information on file?  
We will not keep your information for longer than is necessary and will take steps to ensure that it is kept up to date. You may also update your information from time to time. You have a right under the Data Protection Act 1998 to ask what information we hold about you. You can do this by writing to us at: 

Fast Web Media Ltd,  
1st Floor, Armstrong House,  
Manchester Technology Centre,  
Oxford Road, Manchester,  
M1 7ED

6\. Will we transfer your information outside of the UK?  
Please note that we may have to send your information to locations outside the UK or the EEA, such as the USA, possibly including countries whose protection of personal information may not be as high as that in the UK. If your information is transferred to a service provider or agent in another country, we will make sure that the service provider or agent agrees to apply the same levels of protection, as we are required to apply to information held in the UK. We will ensure that your information is only used for the purpose of providing a service to us. 

7\. How we communicate with you.  
If you contact us or we contact you by telephone, we may:  

  * record the call so that we can check instructions;

  * listen to calls to help us monitor the quality of our service.

We will send e-mails to the e-mail address you have given us. We will not be responsible if anyone else gets access to your e-mails. If you send us an e-mail, you cannot assume that it has reached us until we return an e-mail acknowledging receipt. Please note that the Internet is not a completely secure medium. Please tell us if you find any failure, delay or error in sending or receiving e-mail. 

8\. Any queries?  
If you have any queries or concerns about privacy on the 4thegame.com site please contact us at 

Fast Web Media Ltd,  
Fast Web Media Ltd,  
1st Floor, Armstrong House,  
Manchester Technology Centre,  
Oxford Road, Manchester,  
M1 7ED
